sims4studio.com 2018-10-18

# Privacy Policy | Sims 4 Studio

Sims 4 Studio is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the Website. Sims 4 Studio created this Privacy Policy to give You confidence as You visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.

This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website and not to any websites of third parties ("Third-Party Websites"), which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.

Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below.

1\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Sims 4 Studio does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Sims 4 Studio obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, Sims 4 Studio will immediately contact the host of this website (Forums.net) that controls the database and request that this information be removed. Because Sims 4 Studio does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, Sims 4 Studio has no such information to use or disclose to third parties. Sims 4 Studio has designed this Privacy Policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

a. Traffic Data. Sims 4 Studio may automatically gather information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Website; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively "Traffic Data").

b. "Cookies" are text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit or certain emails that you open. A Cookie acts as a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website. Sims 4 Studio uses Cookies.

c. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to Sims 4 Studio. Other third party ad vendors listed here: [_https://support.google.com/3pascertification/table/4572577_](https://support.google.com/3pascertification/table/4572577) may serve ads via Google AdSense. You may opt out of these ads by visiting [_http://www.aboutads.info_](http://www.aboutads.info/) or their respective website if they are not on [_http://www.aboutads.info_](http://www.aboutads.info/).

d. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visits to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.

e. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

You can learn more about how to delete or control cookies at _www.aboutcookies.org_.

f. Personal Information. In order for You to use certain of the Website services, You will be asked to provide Sims 4 Studio certain information that personally identifies You ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) "Contact Data" (such as Your e-mail address, website URLs, and instant messaging screen names); and (2) "Demographic Data" (such as Your date of birth and gender). In each case, You will be asked to provide Personal Information; _The only required information you need to provide to use this website is a viable email address._ The website will not gather any of this information surreptitiously. 

You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that a viable email address is required to become a member at this site. If you choose to not become a member of the site you may continue to use the site but certain areas of the site will not be available to you.

You are required to create a personal profile, which may include Personal Information. Personal Information contained in personal profiles is available and accessible to all visitors of the Website. The Website contains features that permit You to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other, including Your Personal Information. Any information that You choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which Sims 4 Studio is unable to exercise control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose Your Personal Information by means of such features, and You agree to assume all responsibility for doing so. We encourage members to use discretion in the type and amount of personal information they share in the online environment and to keep in mind that this is a PG-13 site.

3\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES

a. Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies

Sims 4 Studio analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help Sims 4 Studio better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Sims 4 Studio is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements. Sims 4 Studio does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information.

b. Personal Information

i. Generally. Sims 4 Studio uses Your Contact Data to send You occasional updates about the Sims 4 Studio custom content creation tool and forum activities, and to contact You when necessary in connection with the Services. You are free to opt out of receiving these email updates. Sims 4 Studio shares Demographic Data with its advertisers and marketing partners so that such third-parties may provide You with advertisements tailored to Your interests.

ii. Disclosure Practices.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, and under the following circumstances, Sims 4 Studio will keep Your Personal Information private, and will not share it with third parties.

Disclosure in Connection with Services. Sims 4 Studio discloses the Personal Information you have provided to those who help it provide services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as, but not limited to, ad serving, hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security.

Opt-in Consent for Third Party Offers. Sims 4 Studio is not responsible for the policies or practices of the proprietors of any Third Party Offers You opt-in to receive. You are under no obligation to co-register for or opt-in to receive any Third Party Offer.

By Law or to Protect Rights. Sims 4 Studio discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Sims 4 Studio believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Sims 4 Studio, third-parties or the public at large.

4\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our host, Forums.net has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information.

5\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you wish to change Your Personal Information, please visit your account profile.

6\. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

Sims 4 Studio neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy.

7\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Sims 4 Studio reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. Unless Sims 4 Studio obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy.

Effective Date: August 12., 2015
